复习练习 F：三词短语总结。请重复下面的句子，
Review exercise f three word phrase summary Repeat the following sentences
write your own sentences at the bottom carrying over the same examples you used
继续沿用上一练习的例子。
in the previous exercise one a really short nail a long fingernail a fingernail
clipper to a big chocolate cake a thin pancake a pancake shop three a long hot
bath a hot tub, a hot tub maker. Four, a long boring drive, a new hard drive, a
hard drive holder. Five, a broken back door, a long backbone, a backbone massage.
Six, four slick cards, a new playing card, a playing card rack. Seven, a small black
spot, a bright spotlight, a spotlight stand, 8, a well-written book, an open
phone book, a phone book listing, 9, a blind salesman, a blind salesman, 10, a
light housekeeper, a lighthouse keeper 11 a greenhouse plant a greenhouse plant